aforarcade.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Arcade

**Privacy Policy**

References in the Privacy Policy to “ARCADE,” “we,” “us,” or “our” are to Arcade Clothing LLP. Any person accessing or using the websites located at www.aforarcade.com, and any other website(s) owned and/or operated by ARCADE and any of their associated web pages (collectively, the "Website") is referred to as "you" or “your”.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you. You should check this page regularly to take notice of any changes we may have made.

**YOUR DATA**

We will collect your data when you join our mailing list and when you make an order with us.

Collection of Data

We ask for your e-mail address when you subscribe to our Mailing List. When you make a purchase on our Website, in addition to the above, we also ask for your name, delivery address, contact information and payment method details.

Usage of Data

Your data will enable us to fulfil your order, to notify you about important functionality changes and for statistical or survey purposes to improve this website and our services to you. We will also email you from time to time about our new collections and details of promotions and special offers from ARCADE. If you do not wish to be contacted for these purposes, you may unsubscribe to the mailing list with the link provided at the bottom of those e-mails.

Confidentiality of Data

Being committed to maintaining your privacy, we will not sell your e-mail address, name, delivery address, contact information, payment method details or any other personal information to any third party without your permission. We will only disclose your data upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

**COOKIES**

A Cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to enable you to proceed to checkout at any time and to personalize your online experience. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website. Refer to the Help content of your browser for more information on selecting or deselecting Cookies.

If you are not happy with the way that we use cookies then you should delete our cookies having visited the site, or you should browse our Website using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.).

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may from time to time include third party links on our Website. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We encourage you to review those policies when you visit those sites. This Privacy Policy Statement only covers our Website and does not cover any other website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

**INDEMNITY**

You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless ARCADE, its third-party vendors, manufacturers, agents, distributors, corporate affiliates, officers, directors, and employees from and against any and all claims, actions, demands, liabilities, costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable attorney's fees, (a) made by any third party due to or arising out of any Content Submitted, posted, or otherwise provided by you to the Network, ARCADE and/or its third party licensors, licensees or advertisers, and/or (b) resulting from your breach of any provision of these Terms of Use, any warranty you provide herein, or otherwise arising in any way out of your use of the Network or purchase of the products or services therefrom.  ACRADE reserves the right to take exclusive control and defense of any such claim otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate fully with ARCADE in asserting any available defenses.

Last edited Jun 2017
